Toggle navigation [](https://skolera.com/en)

* [About Us](javascript:void(0);)
* [Platform](javascript:void(0);)

* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated 22/02/2018  
  
This privacy policy covers the services accessed using Skolera ULP. Skolera ULP is a cloud-based Unified learning Platform for use by K-12 educational institutions. The platform provides suite of tools including a school management, a learning management and a content management systems. Students, Employees and parents can access Skolera ULP through their school account.  
  
This Privacy Policy describes Skolera ULP’s privacy practices in relation to information that is provided to us by the schools as part of the initial provisioning process or added by school employees as part of the normal usage of the system.  
  
Skolera ULP adheres to strict information collection, use and disclosure policy and does not allow the sharing of this information to third parties.  

Information We Collect
----------------------

Personal Information  
“Personal Information” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual.  
  
Skolera does not collect any information for its own use or to share with other parties. Personal information is provided by the school as part of the employee, student and parent records.  

Other Information
-----------------

For the purpose of improving and enhancing its service, Skolera ULP collects and analyzes data on how the applications are used in the aggregate (how groups of people use Skolera ULP). As true of most Web Sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We also use tracking technologies from third party service providers (as described below) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information you interacted with. We may link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We do not share this information with third parties - for more information on third party service providers, see section below.  
  
Information on individual usage of the system, including but not limited to individual IP addresses, may be analyzed on a case-specific basis to resolve a technical difficulty or to assist in resolving or investigating any misuse of the service; also, such individual usage information is also accessible to your school administration and may be used to assist in the investigation of fraudulent, abusive, or criminal activity or any other use of Skolera ULP that violates your school's rules or policies.  

Tracking Technologies
---------------------

Cookies and other Similar Technologies: Technologies such as cookies, tags and scripts are used by Skolera ULP and our tracking utility partners. These technologies are used to make it easier for you to navigate our site, to store your passwords so you don’t have to enter it more than once, analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements throughout the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.  

Third Party Service Providers
-----------------------------

We work with a number of third party service providers to help improve the quality of our service. These third parties do not share your information with any other third parties.  

* Skolera ULP uses the following third party services:  
      
    * **Google Analytics** - Google Analytics is an analytics service used to help analyze your use of our application, Main Domain and subdomains and allow us to improve communication. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our application. Google Analytics does not share your information with any other third parties.

Review and Deletion of Your Child’s Information
-----------------------------------------------

Parents have the right to refuse the site further contact with their child and to have access to their child's information and to have it deleted by contacting the school administrator.  
  
Parents have the right to consent to the site's use of the child's personal information without having to consent to its disclosure of that information to third parties by contacting the school administrator.  
  
If you are the parent and guardian of a student using Skolera ULP, and cease to agree with Skolera ULP's terms of use and privacy policy at some point in the future, you may opt-out by contacting (a) your Subscriber (typically your school) Skolera ULP administrator or (b) Skolera ULP a [support@Skolera.com.](mailto:support@Skolera.com)  
  
If yours or your child's personally identifiable information changes, you may correct, update, or delete it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting your school administration.  
  
We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  

Internet Privacy & Security
---------------------------

Skolera ULP and your school work together to protect the online privacy of all of your school community members that use Skolera ULP, including students, parents, teachers, and administrators. This privacy policy and Skolera ULP’s information collection and security practices have been authorized by your school, and Skolera ULP strives to manage your school's internet services in a secure manner. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and “hacker-proof,” and Skolera ULP cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information managed by the site, whether transmitted to Skolera ULP by you, your school, or your teacher. Skolera ULP shall not be liable if a security breach occurs, if the site malfunctions, or if information is misused or mismanaged in any way to your detriment or the detriment of a third party, whether by Skolera ULP, your school, your teacher, or an unauthorized third party.  

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement.  
  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to how we use your personal information or personal information collected from children under age 13, we will notify you prior to the change becoming effective, by means of notice on our home page.  

Disclosure
----------

We may disclose your or your child’s personally identifiable information in connection with business transfers and purchases. As we continue to develop our business we may buy or sell business divisions or companies, we may merge or combine with another company, or our company itself and/or all or a significant part of its assets may be acquired by another company. We may provide any information we have to a potential counter-party in any such potential transaction. If such a transaction is completed, your or your child’s personally identifiable information may be one of the transferred and shared business assets. In the event that information is shared in this manner, notice will be posted on our Site.  
  
In this event this privacy policy will continue to apply unless we contact you and ask you to opt in to any changes before they are implemented.  
  
We may also share de-identified and/or aggregated data with others for their own uses.  
  
We reserve the right to disclose your or your child's personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.  

Links to Other Sites
--------------------

If you click on a link to a third-party site, you will leave Skolera ULP and be redirected to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as Skolera ULP. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third-party website that is linked to the Skolera ULP site, you should read that site's privacy statement before providing any personally identifiable information.  

Subscribe now to get the latest free educational resources of Skolera

USA Office: Massachusetts

UK Office: London

MEA Office: Cairo

KSA Office: Riyadh

2017 © All Rights Reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://skolera.com/en/privacy-policy) | [Terms of Use](https://skolera.com/en/terms-of-use)
